Guide to the Chiron Review Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 1999 Acquisition, 1979-1999, undated; 13.66; (20 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Poetry events and music performances
    - "Linda's Two Short Stories: 'The Girl with the Ruby Nipples' and 'The Red Camilla Mystery' + Sapphos", 1999 June 20; 1; 00:40:52; The program is distorted at times. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362569)
    - "Lynx: Haiku (wu songs) Sapphic Sisters Wokshop / Linda..wu songs", 1998 May 31; 1; 00:40:29; A high amount of background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. A warble can be heard on the program. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362577)
    - "Lynx Quicksilver: Songs & Compositions / Lynx Plus Linda Joan talk and read Haiku to Michael!!", 1996 February; 1; 01:02:29; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362585)
    - "Ophthalmic Sympothalia + One Hour of Sapphic Workshop", 1999 July 11; 1; 01:05:18; The program is distorted at times. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362437)
    - "'Works' by M. Sonnenfeld", undated; 1; 00:11:03; The program is distorted at times. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002099362593)
    - "Sapphic Sisters", 1999 August 1; 1; This tape was not digitized due to damage. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002099362601)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Workshop / Judy Collins", 1998 June 14; 1; 01:03:10; A high amount of background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. The audio is not always clear on the program. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002099362619)
    - "Sapphic Workshop / Solstice Party...Tape #1 / Linda Zeiser, San Leandro, CA", 1997 December 21; 1; 01:34:19 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002099362627)
    - "Solstice party...Tape #2 / Linda Zeiser, San Leandro, CA", undated; 1; 01:34:29; The program is distorted at times. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002099362643)
    - "Short Tales / Poems from the Mind of John Kurluk", undated; 1; 01:01:48 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002099362635)
    - "Flippin' the Script: Rap Meets Poetry", undated; 1; 00:51:55; An echo can be heard on the tape. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002099362650)
      "Introduction" - Bob Holman
      "Harlem Sweeties" - 17
      "Processions" Tish Benson
      "What I Got is Gonna Last" - Kool Kim
      "Love Poems" - Bob Holman
      "Open" - Sonja Sohn
      "Kickin' It All Around" - Dasez featuring Richie D'Tempo
      "Space" - Sekou Sundiata
      "Nigger-Reecan Blues" - Wille Perdomo
      "OS-SOS-SAROS" - Edwin Torres
      "Supreme" - Samantha Coerbell
      "My Baby's Mother" - High Priest
      "What is Hip Hop?" - Greg Tate
      "Regurgitations" - Mikah
      "No Respect for Life" - Essence Donn
      "Every Time I Say Now" - 17
      "Why Lie?" - Sha-Key
      "Well" - Everton Sylvester
      "Howl in Japanese" - Nakagaki Hisafumi (a.k.a. 'Howlin' Tommy)
      "Letter Word Terminology" - Murder One
      "Night Fears" - Bob Holman
    - Wammo. "Fat Headed Stranger", undated; 1; 00:42:54 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002099362668)
      "Homage to the Ramones"
      "Batman"
      "Children of the Corn Nuts"
      "Hack"
      "There is Too Much Light in this Bar"
      "Put Your Hands Against the Car"
      "Open Letter '92"
      "Cat Head Biscuits"
      "Salty"
      "Do I Look Fat in This?"
      "This May Sound Kind of Weird"
      "The Walls Smile (for J.D.M.)"
      "Empty Bottle"
      "A Real Gone Guy"
      "Fall on Rome"
      "Unprotected Menage A Trois"
      "Charles Bukowski's Dead"
    - "in/word/out" Zeitgeist Productions, 1992; YCALMSS836_0003; 1; 00:58:48 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317162)
      A letter addressed to Gerald Locklin, poetry editor of Chiron Review, from Rocco Spagnola, President of Rococo Records, is included with this video. It is dated 1994-12-12 and reads: Dear Gerry: Thank you for the tremendous job that you did at the recording session on Saturday, 10 December 1994. I didn't think it would be possible for me to enjoy listening to poetry as much as I did. I know Stan and Mike McDonald feel the same way. Stan and Mike and I are going to think about music for some of the poetry and I am going to send a copy of the cassette to our cinematographer, Russ Brandt, to start thinking about a video to be released along with the compact disc and the cassette. I'm going to send a tape to our artist, Eric Yaple, so that he can begin preparing the art work for the project. I shall contact you shortly about meeting sometime in late December or early January to discuss our plans for the project and to take your views into account. Once again, thank you for a great experience. Cordially, Rocco Spagnola.
    - "Edward Field Reading at Long Beach", undated; YCALMSS836_0004; 1; 02:01:49; The video ends suddenly at the end of the tape. (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317170)
    - "Fred & Joan", undated; YCALMSS836_0005; 1; 00:32:55 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317188)
    - "Michael Hathaway Film by Eric Breitbart," Mark Weber, Todd Moore, Michael Vlatkovich Group, Albuquerque, 1994 March 6; YCALMSS836_0006; 1; 01:42:11 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317196)
    - "The Poetry of Dr. John Gilgun Missouri Western State College", 1995 February 6; YCALMSS836_0007; 1; 00:09:40 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317204)
      A typewritten note from John Gilgun of Missouri Western State College, dated 1995-02-07, is housed with the tape. It reads: Mike: If you need Super VHF for greater "resolution" in the tape, we can provide it. Just let me know. John
    - "Poetry by Tony Moffeit" Poetry Reading at the University of Southern Colorado, Hifi Monoaural Sound, 28 minutes, 1995 May 4; YCALMSS836_0008; 1; 00:29:29 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317212)
    - Knott, Doug. "Psychic Defense Training For Ex-Lovers", undated; YCALMSS836_0009; 1; 00:02:54 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317220)
      A typewritten copy of the poem is included with the tape.
    - "Seaward" and "Fish Story", undated; YCALMSS836_0010; 1; 00:11:25 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317238)
    - Small Dogs Bark 3. "Night of the Living Sidemen"; "In the Hebrew Cemetery"; and "I Become Surreal At an Art Opening", undated; ycalmss836_0011; 1; 00:08:50 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317246)
      A typewritten copy of all three poems are included with the tape.
    - "Virginia Love Long reading for Michael Hathaway", undated; YCALMSS836_0012; 1; 00:17:59 (Box 50, Item barcode 39002102317253)
    - "Wings / That Which Takes Flight", undated; YCALMSS836_0013; 1; 00:03:43 (Box 150)
      A typewritten copy of the poem by Laurel Ann Bogen, is included with the tape.
      Restricted fragile material.
    - Ford, Michael C. "Motel Cafe", 1 33 1/3 vinyl sound disc (Box 51 (Record album storage))
- November 2002 Acquisition, 1984-2002, undated; 20.17; (26 boxes)
  Boxes 75-77 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence
    - Unsorted, 2 (Box 53)
    - Hilton, Barbara Wood (Box 53)
    - Weeks, Daniel (Box 53)
  - Chiron Review Issues
    - Chiron Review 48, 51-59, 11 3.5 inch computer disks
      - CR #48 disk 1, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0001; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #48 disk 2, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0002; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #51, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0003; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #52, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0004; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #53, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0005; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #54, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0006; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #55 Autumn, 1998 mh., 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0007; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #56 Winter, 1998 Ruth Moon Kempher 10-27-98, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0008; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #57 Spring '99, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0009; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #58 (summer 1999), 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0010; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR #59 Autumn, 1999, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0011; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 60 (1999 winter), 7 (Box 53)
    - Chiron Review 60 (1999 winter), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #60, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0012; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 60 (1999 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 70 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 61 (2000 spring), 9 (Box 53)
    - Chiron Review 61 (2000 spring), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR 61, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0013; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 62 (2000 summer), 8 (Box 53)
    - Chiron Review 62 (2000 summer), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #62 summer, 2000, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0014; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 63 (2000 winter), 8 (Box 54)
    - Chiron Review 63 (2000 winter), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR 63 winter, 2000, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0015; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 63 (2000 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 70 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 64 (2001 spring), 7 (Box 54)
    - Chiron Review 64 (2001 spring), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #64, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0016; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 64 (2001 spring) (mechanicals) (Box 70 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 65 (2001 summer), 8 (Box 54)
    - Chiron Review 65 (2001 summer), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #65, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0017; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 65 (2001 summer) (mechanicals) (Box 70 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 66 (2001 autumn), 10 (Box 55)
    - Chiron Review 66 (2001 autumn), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #66 8/26/01, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0018; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 66 (2001 autumn) (mechanicals), 2 (Box 71 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 67 (2001 winter), 10 (Box 55)
    - Chiron Review 67 (2001 winter), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR 67, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0019; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 67 (2001 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 71 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 68 (2001 spring), 8 (Box 55)
    - Chiron Review 68 (2001) spring, 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR 68 8-1-99, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0020; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 68 (2002 spring) (mechanicals) (Box 71 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 69 (2002 summer), 8 (Box 56)
    - Chiron Review 69 (2002 summer), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #69, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0021; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review 69 (2002 summer) (mechanicals) (Box 71 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 70 (2002 autumn), 10 (Box 56)
    - Chiron Review 70 (2002 autumn), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #70, (autumn 2002), 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0022; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (mechanicals), 3 (Box 72 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (correspondence), 14 (Box 56)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (correspondence), 24 3.5 inch computer disks
      - CR - Letters 7+8/01, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0023; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review e-mail corresp. July 22. Aug. 6, 2002, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0024; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review e-mail letters June 6-25, 2002, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0025; 1 (Box 78)
      - 1999 Letters Jan. 1-May 31, 1999, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0026; 1 (Box 78)
      - Letters 1999 June 1-Oct.5, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0027; 1 (Box 78)
      - Letters Chiron Review Oct. 6, 1999-12/31/99, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0028; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence July/aug 2000, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0029; 1 (Box 78)
      - Letters 1/1/2000-9/23/01 Chiron Review, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0030; 1 (Box 78)
      - mjh Letters 1998, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0031; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR cr letters 1998, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0032; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR letters 98 Disk 2, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0033; 1 (Box 78)
      - Letters 1997, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0034; 1 (Box 78)
      - Letters Chiron Review 04/_/02-, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0035; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review e-mail letters 12/28/01-05/10/02, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0036; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review letters Jan. 2002, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0037; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR e-mail Letters to Jan. 5, 2002, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0038; 1 (Box 78)
      - CR Letters 5/17/01-9/20/01, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0039; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review Michael Hathaway, Ed. 702 N. Prairie St. John, KS 67576-1516 Letters Feb, 2001 Chorlton 2/4/00, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0040; 1 (Box 78)
      - Letters -Chiron Review 03/2001- full, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0041; 1 (Box 78)
      - Letters (e-mail only) Oct. 2000 - Feb. 2001 Chiron Review Michael Hathaway, Ed. 702 N. Prairie St. John, KS 67576-1516, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0042; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence May/June 2000 Michael Hathaway, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0043; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review mjh e-mail correspondence May 18, 2002 to June 5 and June 27 to June 29-Aug. 19 2002, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0044; 1 (Box 78)
      - Chiron Review Letters, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0045; 1 (Box 78)
      - Letters 09/24/01-, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0046; 1 (Box 78)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (correspondence), 30 (Box 57)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (correspondence), 32 (Box 58)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (correspondence), 8 (Box 59)
  - Chiron Review Chapbooks
    - Crouch, Evelyn Bell. Crossing the Caloosahatchee (Box 59)
    - Eaton, David. Queasy. Carillo, John Paul. Flavor 49 and Other Stories (Box 59)
    - Heim, Scott. Saved from Drowning (Box 59)
    - Holt, Rochelle. Bolts: Fracture Sonnets (Box 59)
    - Holt, Rochelle and Long, Virginia Love. Infamous in Our Prime (Box 59)
  - Writings by Michael Hathaway
    - "Calm Blue Sea", 1 (Box 60)
    - Cosmic Children, 11 (Box 60)
    - Chiron Review / The Kindred Spirit anthology (draft), [1992]; 9 (Box 59)
    - Chiron Review / The Kindred Spirit anthology (permissions), 1992; 5 (Box 60)
    - Chiron Review / The Kindred Spirit anthology (other papers), 1992-1998; 6 (Box 60)
    - "Floating Above the Masses", 1 (Box 60)
    - "Rainbows & Thunder", 1 (Box 60)
  - Other Writings
    - Alexander, Jonathan. "Broken Things" (Box 60)
    - Alexander, Jonathan. "Towards Democracy" (Box 60)
    - Beard, David. "Dreaming in the Midwest" (Box 60)
    - Bell, Evelyn Louise. " I Remember the Sweet Sting" (Box 60)
    - Bernstein, Bernie. "A Jaunt Through the Millennium" (Box 60)
    - Bernstein, Elizabeth. "Many Moons Rising", 2 (Box 60)
    - Bernstein, J. B. "Bone to Bone" (Box 60)
    - Black, Candace. "The Presidential Gate" (Box 60)
    - Brown, Juanita. "Flowers in Hell" (Box 60)
    - Buege, Bill. Unidentified (Box 60)
    - Catalano, Mike. "Silent Thunder", 2 (Box 60)
    - Catlin, Alan. "The Waters of Oblivion", 3 (Box 60)
    - Colebank, Shannon. "Death of Culture" (Box 60)
    - Cordova, Johnny. "Leaving the World of Boys" (Box 60)
    - D'Amadeus. "Tales of a Princess Henk" (Box 60)
    - Dannov, David Mark. "Civilization is a Clown Smiling in the Mirror", 2 (Box 60)
    - Dannov, David Mark. "Even in the Spring the Death Bird Calls My Name" (Box 60)
    - Dannov, David Mark. "From Heaven to Hell - Laughter in Between" (Box 60)
    - Dannov, David Mark. Unidentified poems, 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - David Mark Dannov poems and art 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0047; 1 (Box 78)
    - Dashevsky, Evan. "Absolute Nihilism & Extreme Misogyny" (Box 60)
    - Eastwood, Robert. "Crows & Kites" (Box 60)
    - Eastwood, Robert. "You Don't Run Easily Across the Yalu" (Box 60)
    - Eiseminger, Skip. Unidentified (Box 60)
    - Elliott, William. "Testaments" (Box 60)
    - Elkins, Emory. "The Green Radiator Odes" (Box 60)
    - Everton, Terry. "Lifting a Toast to Sausage Lint and Monty's Phlegm" (Box 60)
    - Fairchuk, Sherry. "The Palace of Ashes" (Box 61)
    - Fitts, Susan Love. "Licking the Bones Dry" (Box 61)
    - Fogle, Andy. "Records Are Made To Be Broken" (Box 61)
    - Forehand, Sara Lee Smith-Wicks. "Remember Family; Always Remember; Never Forget Family" (Box 61)
    - Freeman, Jessica. "New Orleans Dizzy Spit" (Box 61)
    - Galván, Alicia Zavala. "Sensual Satin (Seda Sensual)" (Box 61)
    - Gilgun, John. "Dancing the Darkness into Light" (Box 61)
    - Glade, Jon Forrest. "Photographs of the Jungle, 3rd ed." (Box 61)
    - Goodwyne, Owen. "Centaur" (Box 61)
    - Graziano, Nathan. "Frostbite" (Box 61)
    - Gurkin, Kathyrn Bright. "Afterimages: Poems, 1990-2000", 2 (Box 61)
    - Hamilton, Carol. "Breaking Bread, Breaking Silence" (Box 61)
    - Harmon, Jean. "From Puck's Notebook" (Box 61)
    - Harmon, Jean. "Songs from St. Augustine" (Box 61)
    - Hart, William. "Hard Bucks: A Blue Collar Odyssey" (Box 61)
    - Hathaway, Michael, editor. "Gay and Lesbian Anthology" (Box 61)
    - Hayes, Jonathan, editor. "Over the Transom" (Box 61)
    - Hilton, Barbara. "Women/War" (Box 61)
    - Holstad, Scott. "The Napalmed Soul", 2 (Box 61)
    - Holt, Rochelle L. "Caution: Child at Play", 2 (Box 61)
    - Holt, Rochelle L. "Contemporary Multi-Ethnic Novels by Women Coming of Age Together in the New America", 2 (Box 61)
    - Holt, Rochelle Lynn. "Evening the Score" (Box 61)
    - Holt, Rochelle Lynn, editor. "Sharon Spencer: A Memorial", 2 (Box 61)
    - Holt, Rochelle Lynn. "The Weight of Rain", 3 (Box 61)
    - Holt, Rochelle Lynn. "Whispering Secrets", 2 (Box 61)
    - Holt, Rochelle Lynn. "Wound", 5 (Box 61)
    - Howling Wolf. "German Requiem" (Box 61)
    - Howling Wolf. "Rainy Day Women" (Box 61)
    - Hughes, Sally Page. "E'Port", 2 (Box 61)
    - Igrejas, Manuel. "A Sink Full of Dirty Poems" (Box 62)
    - Inman, Will. "A Resonance of Begetting" (Box 62)
    - Jackson, Lori. "Scat" (Box 62)
    - Jackson, Lori. Unidentified, 2 (Box 62)
    - Jay, Alice. "Stepping Stones", 2 (Box 62)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Ephemera" (Box 62)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "On Being Haunted by Dame Edith Sitwell", 2 (Box 62)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon, editor. "To Life! Occasions of Praise" (Box 62)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Watermark Angels", 2 (Box 62)
    - Knecht, Tom. "Woman of Spice: Yuki" (Box 62)
    - Knight, John Cantey. "A Book of Whores (Devotionals for the Flesh)" (Box 62)
    - Kraft, Eugene. "I'm Not a Yankee-Doodle Dandy! Poems from Kansas", 2 (Box 62)
    - Last, Curtis. "The Adventure in Travel" (Box 62)
    - Laws, Kyle. "Wildwood" (Box 62)
    - Lechevsky, Julie. Unidentified (Box 62)
    - Lerner, Linda, editor. "Poets on the Line: A Continuing Anthology, Nos 9 & 10 (the millennium issue)" (Box 62)
    - Leslie, Naton. "The Last Best Motif" (Box 62)
    - Lipchik, Elliot O. "Family Fires" (Box 62)
    - Lockie, Ellaraine. "Coloring Outside the Lines" (Box 62)
    - Long, Virginia Love. "Hanging With Mary Jane", 2 (Box 62)
    - Lyons, Larry D. "Freudian Dream Interpretation for Poets", 2 (Box 62)
    - Mangeot, André. "Natural Causes" (Box 62)
    - McLean, Susan. "Stranger than Fiction" (Box 62)
    - McDaris, Catfish. "Pterodactyl Soup" (Box 62)
    - McFarland, Ron. "The Mad Waitress Poems" (Box 62)
    - Moon, Janell. "Part Des Anges (The Angel's Portion): Poems of Surviving a Friends Suicide" (Box 62)
    - Mulrooney, Chirstopher. "2000" (Box 62)
    - O'Connell, Richard. "American Orbits" (Box 62)
    - O'Connell, Richard. "Fractals" (Box 62)
    - O'Connell, Richard. "Selected Epigrams" (Box 62)
    - Olds-Ellingson, Alice. "Alice's Strange Bedfellows", 2000 (Box 62)
    - Olds-Ellingson, Alice. "Murder 123" (Box 62)
    - Penfold, Nita. "Loreen Says" (Box 62)
    - Penick, Robert L. "Blue Forms" (Box 62)
    - Perkinson, James W. "Dreaming Moorish" (Box 62)
    - "Photographing Snow Melt" (Box 62)
    - Ricci, Robert. "The Nine Agents" (Box 62)
    - Riyeff, Jake. "Everyday", 2 (Box 62)
    - Roberts, P. J., editor. "Poetry for Peace" (Box 63)
    - Rocheloeau, Linda. "Like Butterflies We Play Endlessly" (Box 63)
    - Ryan, Sheri. "The Magic of Words" (Box 63)
    - Sadin, Marjorie. "The Threads from Which We Fly" (Box 63)
    - Sadler, Lynn Veach. "Spam Maps for Golden Rivers" (Box 63)
    - Sams, Ed. "California Haiku" (Box 63)
    - Sapp, D. David. "The Dead Orchard" (Box 63)
    - Schmitz, Barbara. "How Much Our Dancing Has Improved", 2 (Box 63)
    - Sellers, Heather. "When I Was Her" (Box 63)
    - Shaffer, Eric Paul. "Living at the Monastery, Working in the Kitchen" (Box 63)
    - Shipley, Vivian. "#69" (Box 63)
      Empty folder
    - Shipley, Vivian. "When There is No Shore", 2 (Box 63)
    - Sienkiewicz, Linda K. "In Lavender" (Box 63)
    - Sloboda, Nicholas. "Currents" (Box 63)
    - Smith, Jacqueline. "My G-Rated Life" (Box 63)
    - Smith, Jena. "I Sing at the Millennium" (Box 63)
    - Smith, Michael. "Late Charges on a Touch of Partial Proof" (Box 63)
    - Smith, Michael S. "Mommy's Calling" (Box 63)
    - Smith-Soto, Mark. "Body of a Dream" (Box 63)
    - Smits, Ronald F. "Bayonne" (Box 63)
    - Snider, Clifton. "The Alchemy of Opposites", 5 (Box 63)
    - Soil, Sophie. "The Reality of Being" (Box 63)
    - Solensten, John M. "Awakening Before Sleep" (Box 63)
    - Sonenschein, David. "Pedophiles on Parade v.1" (Box 63)
    - Sonenschein, David. "Pedophiles on Parade v.2" (Box 63)
    - Spencer, Sharon. "Voice from the Earth", 4 (Box 63)
    - Stoller, Necca. "Hard to Come By" (Box 63)
    - Sturley, Joseph. Unidentified (Box 63)
    - Swan, Mark. "Stargazer" (Box 63)
    - Swanberg, Christine Rinaldi. "The Red Lacquer Room", 2 (Box 63)
    - Tham, Hilary. "Reality Check and Other Travel Poems & Art", 2 (Box 64)
    - Thorn, Lee. "Anal Hair and Lesser Matters" (Box 64)
    - Torrence, Thomas. "The Cuetzpali Kiss" (Box 64)
    - Torrence, Thomas. "Flexing Cactus" (Box 64)
    - Vita, Emmanuel. "Halcyon Guernica" (Box 64)
    - Walls, Michael. "The Blues Singer" (Box 64)
    - Watson, Benjamin Campbell. "Black Wax", 4 (Box 64)
    - Watson, Maurice T, Jr. "Eder" (Box 64)
    - Watson, Maurice T., Jr. "Truth", 2 (Box 64)
    - Watson, Maurice T., Jr. "Truth vol. 2", 2 (Box 64)
    - Watson, Maurice T., Jr. "Truth vol.3" (Box 64)
    - Wheeler, Gerald R. "Tracks" (Box 64)
    - Wheeler, Gerald R. "Travlin' Still" (Box 64)
    - White, Anthony Russell. "You Wouldn't Appreciate Lu Wuh's Tea" (Box 64)
    - Wilensky, Ben. "18 Sea Poems" (Box 64)
    - Wisniewski, Mark. "Miracle System" (Box 64)
    - Wisniewski, Mark. Unidentified (Box 64)
  - Poetry events and music performances
    Boxes 75-77 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Crocker, Daniel (Box 64)
    - Crocker, Daniel. "The Beer Drinking Hour" #14, undated; 1; 01:34:12; The program is distorted at times. High background noise on the tape can be heard. The program is recorded at a low level on the left channel at 15:28-19:23. The program is recorded at a low level from 41:32-42:56. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362775)
      A note found with the audiocassette reads: "For best results listen to while drunk!"
    - Gustavson, Ira (Box 64)
    - Gustavson, Ira. "Slightly Used Poems", 2000; 1; 01:34:35 (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362783)
      A note found with this audiocassette reads: "Slightly used" simply refers to the fact that some of the poems have already been read or heard.
    - Jackson, Lorri. "Music", undated; 1; 01:31:29; Clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. High frequency background noise can be heard from 1:31:30 until the end of the tape. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362791)
    - McDaris, Steven C. "Catfish" (Box 64)
    - McDaris, Steven C. "Catfish. "Blanketo!", undated; 1; Low level recording on right channel on the tape. Music from previous recording bleeding through or possible background music. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362809)
    - Poetry Rendezvous, 2 (Box 64)
    - Spiro, Bernard (Box 64)
    - Spiro, Bernard. "Everything's Coming up Pansies", undated; 1; 00:03:49 (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362817)
    - "Dystrophy Ellingson" /13 Years of Ellingson fragments", undated; 1; 01:34:51; The program is distorted at times. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362825)
    - "Linda at St. Peters / St. Peter's and Bancroft Hospital", 2001 June; 1; 01:00:35; The program is distorted at times. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362833)
    - "Moon in Pisces Sapphic Workshop Dedicated to Jane and Michael Hathaway", March 5; 1; 01:34:03; The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362841)